

Abstract

I recently received my Bachelor's degree in International Creative Business from Inholland University of Applied Sciences in The Hague. This program uniquely combined creativity with essential business knowledge, equipping me with a solid foundation in creative problem-solving, marketing, and entrepreneurship.

In addition to my academic background, I have a year of valuable customer service experience working for RIFF, an Amsterdam-based company. During this time, I excelled in administrative tasks and honed formal communication skills. I am fluent in both Spanish and English, with additional intermediate proficiency in French, cultivated during my International Baccalaureate studies at the American School of Madrid (ASM).

Furthermore, I have nearly a year of experience at Timberlands, enhancing my interpersonal skills and proficiency in luxury retail operations. I am comfortable taking on additional responsibilities in this field.

Last summer, I broadened my skill set by working at the high-end fine dining restaurant *Calaiza* in Granada, Spain as a restaurant manager, strengthening my communication and social skills.

Growing up in a diplomatic family, I've lived in various countries, including the U.S., Spain, and the Netherlands. This diverse background has given me a unique perspective and advanced linguistic and cultural understanding. I believe I can offer a wealth of experiences, making me a valuable asset to any team.

Skills

Customer Support

- Communication with people
- Content management experience
- Quantitative skills
- Cultural awareness
- Marketing
- Teamwork
- Active listening
- Teaching
- Fast learning
- Fluency in English and Spanish
- Intermediate French
- Design thinking
- Musician

Experiences

Customer Service Specialist for Bakker Oct 2020 - Oct 2021 RIFF Amsterdam, Netherlands

- Listened to client needs and helped identify and secure appropriate services.
- I provided each client with informed and supportive assistance to meet all their needs and build loyalty.
- Improved customer satisfaction rates by resolving difficult customer issues to completion.
- Used multiple resources and tools to evaluate and present solutions.
- Recorded and reported work-related activities to find discrepancies.

Musician April 2018 - May 2018 Clamores Madrid, Spain 2020 Clamores Musician.

- Acted as a piano bar entertainer and provided dynamic, exciting and engaging performances for guests and recruited and supervised additional musical talent to achieve the organization's goals.
- With friends and former teachers, he organized a concert and raised 20,000 euros for a classmate with cerebral palsy at the American School in Madrid.
- He performed cultural shows at the Niño Jesús University Children's Hospital.

Messenger Jan 2020 - March 2020 Home delivery The Hague

- Coordinated and monitored inbound and outbound deliveries, staying on top of delays and other issues.
- Assess needs and allocate resources to meet demand.

Seller -Timberlands The Hague

October 2022 - June 2023

- Work in the retail sector
- Stock management
- Sales
- Store maintenance
- Help customers in a helpful and empathetic manner
- Teamwork
- Take leadership

Waiter - Calaiza La Herradura, España June 2023 - September 2023

- Table service expertise
- Wine and beverage knowledge
- Etiquette and protocol
- Time management
- Teamwork and communication
- Presentation skills
- Customer relationship building
- Hygiene and safety
- Crisis management
- Cultural awareness
- Stress management

Education

American School of Madrid, Madrid, Spain, 06/2019 international Baccalaureate

Inholland University of Applied Sciences, Den Haag, Netherlands, 2023

Title: Creative Business (Marketing)